Jack Douglas Papers
Jack Douglas Papers
1938-1955
Douglas, Jack, 1908-
14.5 linear ft.
Papers of the American author and comedy writer for radio and television. Scripts for radio and television comedies and talk shows (1938-1955).
148948
Biographical History
Jack Douglas (1908-1989) was a well-known gag writer who wrote for such radio and television performers as Bob Hope, Red Skelton, George Gobel, Jimmy Durante, and Jack Paar. He was the author of My Brother Was an Only Child. He was a regular guest on on Jack Paar's shows in the late 1950s and early 1960s and on shows hosted by Merv Griffin, Dick Cavett and Johnny Carson. Douglas was married three times: to Merle Crain, with whom he had a son John and a daughter Marlene; to Marion Hutton, with whom he had a son, Peter; and to Japanese-born singer and comedienne Reiko, with whom he had two sons, Bobby and Timothy. Reiko frequently appeared with him on television.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Jack Douglas Papers, 1938-1955, consist chiefly of writings and a small group of memorabilia.
Memorabilia includes a certificate of appreciation awarded by the Veterans Administration to Douglas's second wife, Marion Hutton, and a copy of a protest made in 1952 to the United States Treasury Department.
Writings are radio, television, and motion picture scripts, a novel and an untitled play. The scripts are, for the most part, mimeographed copies with notes and corrections, and many contain extensive annotations. The word "revised" is used only when it has been found within the script. The abbreviation "rev." indicates that there are corrections and revisions made by hand in the script. "Anno." refers to annotations in the form of notes or pictures. The number of pages given indicates actual number of leaves in a script. Included in the motion picture scripts is a small group of writings by others. Mr. Douglas's relationship to these scripts, as well as to the novel, The Harvey Girls, also included, is not known. The untitled play appears to have been written by Mr. Douglas.
This collection is of particular interest for the way in which the scripts reflect American life during the World War II years. The patriotic efforts of such entertainers as Red Skelton, Bob Hope, Kay Kyser and Jack Carson, among others, are evident. Another point of interest is the titles of songs that were popular during the period covered by these scripts.
Following is a list of radio and television shows with inclusive dates of scripts. Radio shows are indicated by "R" and television shows by "TV."
The Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet (R) Oct 1944-Jan 1945
The American Tobacco Company, Lucky Strike, The Jack Parr Program (R) Aug 1947-Dec 1947
The Borden Show (see The Tommy Riggs Show)
Broadway Open House (TV) Jun 1951-Jul 1951
Campbell's Soups Show, starring Jack Carson (R) Jan 1944-May 1945
Jack Carson Show (R) Sep 1948-Jul 1949
Jack Douglas Show (R) Apr 1945-Jun 1949
Durante--Moore Show (R) Jan 1946-Sep 1946
George Gobel Show (TV) Oct 1954-Mar 1955
Gulf Screen Guild Theatre (R) Oct 1939-Apr 1942
Phil Harris-Alice Faye Show (R) Mar 1954-Jun 1954
Peter Lind Hayes and Mary Healy Show (TV) Dec 1950-Feb 1951
Kay Kyser Show (R) Jun 1945-Sep 1945
Beatrice Lillie Show (TV) May 13, 1951
Mail Call (Armed Forces Radio Service) (R) Dec 19, 1945
Dean Martin and Jerry Lewis Show (R) Nov 15,21,28, 1949
The Pepsodent Program (R) Dec 1938-Jun 1941
The Tommy Riggs Show, continued as The Borden Show, starring Tommy Riggs Jul 1942-May 1946
Sealtest Village Store Program (R) Dec 1947-Jul 1948
Silver Theatre (R) Nov 1940-Nov 1941
The Red Skelton Show (R,TV) Oct 1941-Jan 1955
The Soldiers (TV) Jul 1955-Aug 1955
Sunbrite Smile Parade (R) Jun 1939-Aug 1939
What's New (R) Jan 8, 15, 1944
Ed Wynn Show (TV) Nov 15, 1950
Arrangement of the Collection
The radio and television scripts, which form the largest part of the papers, are arranged under those headings, then alphabetically by show and chronologically within each show, with undated scripts and fragments at the end of each show. Shows are dated whenever possible by actual broadcast date. When a taping date was used, as in the case of some of the Phil Harris-Alice Faye shows, the letter "T" follows the date. The motion picture scripts are arranged alphabetically by title. Miscellaneous scripts in the categories of radio, television, and motion picture scripts are arranged alphabetically at the end of the category.
Related Material
has the papers of a number of radio and television personalities and shows. Please refer to for a complete listing.
Subject and Genre Headings
Popular culture; Radio, television, film; Douglas, Jack, 1908- Archives.; Authors, American.; Radio authorship.; Radio comedies.; Television authorship.; Television comedies.; Radio scripts.; Television scripts.; Authors.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Jack Douglas, 1969.
Inventory
- Memorabilia
  - Certificate of appreciation awarded by the Veterans Administration to Marion Hutton, undated (Box 1)
  - Protest to the United States Treasury Department, 1952 (Box 1)
- Writings
  - Radio Scripts
    - The Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet
      - 1944 Oct 8, anno., rev., 40 p. (Box 1)
      - 1944 Oct 8, revised, 43 p. (Box 1)
      - 1944 Oct 15, anno., 30 p. (Box 1)
      - 1944 Oct 15, revised, anno., 30 p. (Box 1)
      - 1944 Oct 22, anno., 43 p. (Box 1)
      - 1944 Oct 22, revised, 39 p. (Box 1)
      - 1944 Oct 22, fragments, typescript copy, 14 p. (Box 1)
      - 1944 Oct 29, anno., 39 p. (Box 1)
      - 1944 Nov 5, anno., 38 p. (Box 1)
      - 1944 Nov 12, revised, 54 p. (Box 1)
      - 1944 Dec 3, anno., revised, 36 p. (Box 1)
      - 1944 Dec 3, revised, 36 p. (Box 1)
      - 1944 Dec 15, Preview, anno., 42 p. (Box 1)
      - 1944 Dec 17, 41 p. (Box 1)
      - 1944 Dec 24, anno., revised, 42 p. (Box 1)
      - 1944 Dec 24, revised, 40 p. Dec 31, 35 p. (Box 1)
      - 1944 Dec 31, 35 p. (Box 1)
      - 1945 Jan 7, 46 p. (Box 1)
      - 1945 Jan 7, revised, 40 p. (Box 1)
      - 1945 Jan 12, preview, anno., 43 p. (Box 1)
      - 1945 Jan 14, anno., 38 p. (Box 2)
      - Undated fragments, 1945; printed material, typescript copy, 38 p. (Box 2)
    - The American Tobacco Company, Lucky Strike, The Jack Paar Program
      - 1947 Aug 3, revised, anno., 23 p. (Box 2)
      - 1947 Aug 10, revised, 27 p. (Box 2)
      - 1947 Aug 17, anno., revised, 23 p. (Box 2)
      - 1947 Aug 17, revised, anno., revised, 29 p. (Box 2)
      - 1947 Aug 24, Second Revision, anno., 25 p. (Box 2)
      - 1947 Aug 31, anno., revised, 20 p. (Box 2)
      - 1947 Aug 31, revised, anno., revised, 25 p. (Box 2)
      - 1947 Sep 7, anno., revised, 22 p. (Box 2)
      - 1947 Sep 14, anno., revised, 25 p. (Box 2)
      - 1947 Sep 14, revised, 24 p. (Box 2)
      - 1947 Sep 21, anno., revised, 18 p. (Box 2)
      - 1947 Sep 21, revised, revised, 25 p. (Box 2)
      - 1947 Sep 28, anno., 19 p. (Box 2)
      - 1947 Oct 1, anno., revised, 21 p. (Box 2)
      - 1947 Oct 1, revised, 22 p. (Box 2)
      - 1947 Oct 8, anno., revised, 17 p. (Box 2)
      - 1947 Oct 15, anno., revised, 20 p. (Box 2)
      - 1947 Oct 15, revised anno., revised, 25 p. (Box 2)
      - 1947 Oct 22, anno., 20 p. (Box 2)
      - 1947 Oct 22, revised, anno., 25 p. (Box 2)
      - 1947 Oct 29, anno., rev., 20 p. (Box 2)
      - 1947 Oct 29, revised, anno., 25 p. (Box 2)
      - 1947 Nov 5, anno., 20 p. (Box 2)
      - 1947 Nov 5, revised, anno., 23 p. (Box 2)
      - 1947 Nov 12, revised, 19 p. (Box 2)
      - 1947 Nov 12, revised, 21 p. (Box 2)
      - 1947 Nov 19, anno., 20 p. (Box 3)
      - 1947 Nov 19, revised, revised, 25 p. (Box 3)
      - 1947 Nov 26, anno., 23 p. (Box 3)
      - 1947 Nov 26, revised, 25 p. (Box 3)
      - 1947 Dec 3, revised, anno., 24 p. (Box 3)
      - 1947 Dec 10, 18 p. (Box 3)
      - 1947 Dec 10, revised, 23 p. (Box 3)
      - 1947 Dec 17, anno., 17 p. (Box 3)
      - 1947 Dec 17, revised, anno., 24 p. (Box 3)
      - 1947 Dec 24, anno., 16 p. (Box 3)
      - Undated, 1947
        - Script, anno., 18 p. (Box 3)
        - Fragments, printed material, typescript, revised, 2p. (Box 3)
    - Campbell's Soups Show, starring Jack Carson
      - 1944 Jan 3, 25 p. (Box 3)
      - 1944 Jan 10, anno., 25 p. (Box 3)
      - 1944 Aug 23, 27 p. (Box 3)
      - 1944 Aug 30, 26 p. (Box 3)
      - 1944 Sep 13, anno., 28 p. (Box 3)
      - 1944 Sep 20, anno., 27 p. (Box 3)
      - 1944 Sep 27, 25 p. (Box 3)
      - 1944 Nov 8, 23 p. (Box 3)
      - 1944 Nov 15, 26 p. (Box 3)
      - 1944 Nov 22, anno. 25 p. (Box 3)
      - 1944 Nov 29, 28 p. (Box 3)
      - 1944 Dec 6, Story Line, typescript, 1 (Box 3)
      - 1944 Dec 6, 23 p. (Box 3)
      - 1944 Dec 13, anno., 24 p. (Box 3)
      - 1944 Dec 20, 21 p. (Box 3)
      - 1944 Dec 27, anno., 25 p. (Box 3)
      - 1945 Jan 24, anno., 26 p. (Box 3)
      - 1945 Jan 31, anno., 25 p. (Box 4)
      - 1945 Feb 7, anno., revised, 27 p. (Box 4)
      - 1945 Feb 14, anno., 25 p. (Box 4)
      - 1945 Mar 21, 26 p. (Box 4)
      - 1945 Apr 4, anno., 27 p. (Box 4)
      - 1945 May 23, Story Line, typescript copy, 1 p. (Box 4)
    - Jack Carson Show
      - 1948 Sep 28, anno., 25 p. (Box 4)
      - 1948 Oct 8, typescript anno., 35 p. (Box 4)
      - 1948 Oct 15, anno., 23 p. (Box 4)
      - 1948 Oct 15, 27 p. (Box 4)
      - 1948 Oct 20, Preview, anno., 24 p. (Box 4)
      - 1948 Oct 22, revised, 28 p. (Box 4)
      - 1948 Oct 27, anno., 24 p. (Box 4)
      - 1948 Oct 29, anno., 27 p. (Box 4)
      - 1948 Nov 4, anno., 21 p. (Box 4)
      - 1948 Nov 5, anno., rev., 25 p. (Box 4)
      - 1948 Nov 12, anno., rev., 24 p. (Box 4)
      - 1948 Nov 12, 32 p. (Box 4)
      - 1948 Nov 19, 25 p. (Box 4)
      - 1948 Nov 19, anno., 29 p. (Box 4)
      - 1948 Nov 26, 27 p. (Box 4)
      - 1948 Nov 26, anno., 27 p. (Box 4)
      - 1948 Nov 26, 27 p. (Box 4)
      - 1948 Dec 3, 30 p. (Box 4)
      - 1948 Dec 3, 31 p. (Box 4)
      - 1948 Dec 3, anno., 26 p. (Box 4)
      - 1948 Dec 10, anno., rev., 29 p. (Box 4)
      - 1948 Dec 10, 30 p. (Box 4)
      - 1948 Dec 17, revised 27 p. (Box 5)
      - 1948 Dec 24, revised 27 p. (Box 5)
      - 1949 Jan 7, anno., 29 p. (Box 5)
      - 1949 Jan 7, 29 p. (Box 5)
      - 1949 Jan 14, 30 p. (Box 5)
      - 1949 Jan 14, anno., rev., 30 p. (Box 5)
      - 1949 Jan 21, anno., rev., 29 p. (Box 5)
      - 1949 Jan 28, anno., rev., 27 p. (Box 5)
      - 1949 Jan 28, anno., 24 p. (Box 5)
      - 1949 Feb 4, rev., 6 p. (Box 5)
      - 1949 Feb 4, anno., rev., 22 p. (Box 5)
      - 1949 Feb 4, typescript rev., 20 p. (Box 5)
      - 1949 Feb 11, anno., 27 p. (Box 5)
      - 1949 Feb 18, anno., rev., 36 p. (Box 5)
      - 1949 Feb 18, 36 p. (Box 5)
      - 1949 Feb 18, anno., 20 p. (Box 5)
      - 1949 Feb 25, 29 p. (Box 5)
      - 1949 Feb 25, rev., 32 p. (Box 5)
      - 1949 Feb 25, printed material, typescript copy., 28 p. (Box 5)
      - 1949 Mar 4, rev., 37 p. (Box 5)
      - 1949 Mar 11, anno., rev., 36 p. (Box 5)
      - 1949 Mar 11, anno., rev., 33 p. (Box 5)
      - 1949 Mar 11, rev., 13 p. (Box 5)
      - 1949 Mar 18, anno., rev., 33 p. (Box 5)
      - 1949 Mar 18, 30 p. (Box 5)
      - 1949 Mar 25, anno., rev., 32 p. (Box 6)
      - 1949 Mar 25, rev., 31 p. (Box 6)
      - 1949 Apr 1, typescript typescript copy rev., 46 p. (Box 6)
      - 1949 Apr 1, printed material, typescript copy anno., 35 p. (Box 6)
      - 1949 Apr 8, anno., 29 p. (Box 6)
      - 1949 Apr 8, fragment, 7 p. (Box 6)
      - 1949 Apr 8, rev., 24 p. (Box 6)
      - 1949 Apr 15, rev., 28 p. (Box 6)
      - 1949 Apr 15, 27 p. (Box 6)
      - 1949 Apr 22, typescript rev., 13 p. (Box 6)
      - 1949 Apr 22, rev., 29 p. (Box 6)
      - 1949 Apr 22, anno., 30 p. (Box 6)
      - 1949 Apr 28, 35 p. (Box 6)
      - 1949 Apr 28, anno., 30 P. (Box 6)
      - 1949 Apr 28, rev., 30 p. (Box 6)
      - 1949 May 3, 33 p. (Box 6)
      - 1949 May 3, revised fragment, 7 p. (Box 6)
      - 1949 May 13, rev., 33 p. (Box 6)
      - 1949 May 13, anno., 34 p. (Box 6)
      - 1949 May 13, 30 p. (Box 6)
      - 1949 May 20, 33 p. (Box 6)
      - 1949 May 20, 35 p. (Box 6)
      - 1949 May 27, fragment, rev., 9 p. (Box 6)
      - 1949 May 27, rev., 34 p. (Box 6)
      - 1949 Jun 3, anno., 19 p. (Box 6)
      - 1949 Jun 3, rev., 22 p. (Box 6)
      - 1949 Jun 3, 31 p. (Box 6)
      - 1949 Jun 10, rev., 27 p. (Box 7)
      - 1949 Jun 17, rev., 31 p. (Box 7)
      - 1949 Jun 24, rev., 31 p. (Box 7)
      - 1949 Jun 24, fragment, rev., 13 p. (Box 7)
      - 1949 Jun 24, rev., 20 p. (Box 7)
      - 1949 Jul 1, rev., 32 p. (Box 7)
      - 1949 Jul 1, anno., 32 p. (Box 7)
      - Undated, 1949; 6 folders (Box 7)
    - Jack Douglas Show
      - 1945 Apr 5, typescript copy rev., 5 p. (Box 8)
      - 1945 May 1, typescript copy rev., 10 p. (Box 8)
      - 1945 May 22, typescript copy, Incomplete, 17 p. (Box 8)
      - 1945 May 22, 23 p. (Box 8)
      - 1945 Jun 15, anno., 23 p. (Box 8)
      - 1945 Jun 15, revised, anno., 22 p. (Box 8)
      - 1945 Jun 15, Final Master, anno., rev. 23 p. (Box 8)
      - Undated "Crazy Show", 1945; typescript rev., 4 p. (Box 8)
        - Script, typescript rev., 16 p. (Box 8)
        - Script, typescript, anno., 18 p. (Box 8)
    - Durante - Moore Show, starring Jimmy Durante and Garry Moore
      - 1946 Jan 18, revised, anno., 24 p. (Box 8)
      - 1946 Jan 25, anno., 23 p. (Box 8)
      - 1946 Feb 1, revised 25 p. (Box 8)
      - 1946 Feb 8, revised anno., 25 p. (Box 8)
      - 1946 Mar 1, fragments, anno., 17 p. (Box 8)
      - 1946 Mar 1, anno., 24 p. (Box 8)
      - 1946 Mar 22, anno., 21 p. (Box 8)
      - 1946 Mar 22, anno., 27 p. (Box 8)
      - 1946 Apr 3, Sketch, typescript copy., 7 p. (Box 8)
      - 1946 May 3, Garry Moore Spot ts., 4 p. (Box 8)
      - 1946 May 10, Sketch typescript copy. 7 p. (Box 8)
      - 1946 May 17, Sketch typescript 6 p. (Box 8)
      - 1946 May 17, 26 p. (Box 8)
      - 1946 May 24, 28 p. (Box 8)
      - 1946 May 31, Sketch rev., 6 p. (Box 8)
      - 1946 May 31, Durante Spot, 6 p. p. (Box 8)
      - 1946 Jun 7, Douglas Middle typescript copy rev., 4 (Box 8)
      - 1946 Sep 13, Opening typescript rev., 4 p. (Box 8)
      - 1946 Sep 13, Garry Moore Spot typescript rev., 5 p. (Box 8)
      - 1946 Sep 20, rev., 24 p. (one page typescript) (Box 8)
      - Undated, 1946
        - Court Room Scene, typescript rev., 6 p. (Box 8)
        - Sketch, typescript rev., 6 p. (Box 8)
        - Sketch, typescript copy rev., 6 p. (Box 8)
        - Garry Spot Add, typescript rev., 2 p. (Box 8)
        - Add, typescript copy, 2 p. (Box 8)
        - Fragment, typescript copy, 2 p. (Box 8)
    - Gulf Screen Guild Theatre
      - Western Sketch, 1939 Oct 8; typescript copy, 5 p. (Box 8)
      - "Elmer the Great", 1940 Apr 14; version "B," 30 p. (Box 8)
      - "Altar Bound", 1941 Feb 23; first draft, anno., 22 p.; first revision, 24 p. typescript copy, 19 p. (Box 8)
      - "Tight Shoes", 1942 Apr 12; revised, 33 p.; final, rev., 31 p. (Box 8)
    - Phil Harris - Alice Faye Show
      - 1954 Mar 5, rev., 30 p. (Box 9)
      - 1954 Mar 6, anno., rev., 22 p. (Box 9)
      - 1954 Mar 28, anno., rev., 22 p. (Box 9)
      - 1954 Apr 2, anno., rev., 30 p. (Box 9)
      - 1954 Apr 9, anno., rev., 26 p. (Box 9)
      - 1954 Apr 18, anno., rev., 24 p. (Box 9)
      - 1954 Apr 17, anno., rev., 24 p. (Box 9)
      - 1954 Apr 23, anno., 24 p. (Box 9)
      - 1954 Apr 30, anno., 27 p. (Box 9)
      - 1954 May 21, anno., 26 p. (Box 9)
      - 1954 May 8, anno., rev., 28 p. (Box 9)
      - 1954 May 14, anno., rev., 25 p. (Box 9)
      - 1954 Jun 4, anno., rev., 21 p. (Box 9)
      - 1954 Jun 11, anno., rev., 25 p. (Box 9)
      - Undated fragments, 1954; typescript anno., 1 p.; typescript copy rev., 3 p. (Box 9)
    - Kay Kyser's "College of Musical Knowledge", Shows from the summer of 1944 have Phil Harris substituting for Kay Kyser
      - 1944 Jun 28, fragment, typescript, 1 p. (Box 9)
      - 1944 Jul 5, fragment, typescript copy, 3 p. (Box 9)
      - 1944 Jul 26, fragment, typescript, 1 p. (Box 9)
      - 1944 Aug 9, fragment, typescript, 1 p. (Box 9)
      - 1944 Aug 16, fragment, typescript, 1 p. (Box 9)
      - 1944 Aug 23, fragment, typescript, 2 p. (Box 9)
      - 1944 Aug 30, fragment, typescript, 1 p. (Box 9)
      - 1944 Sep 6, fragment, typescript, 2 p. (Box 9)
      - 1944 Sep 20, fragment, typescript, 1 p. (Box 9)
      - 1944 Sep 27, fragment, typescript, 2 p. (Box 9)
      - 1945 Jun 20, Kay Kyser, script, revised, 35 p. (Box 9)
      - 1945 Jul 4, fragment, typescript copy anno., 6 p. (Box 9)
      - 1945 Jul 11, fragment, typescript copy anno., 6 p. (Box 9)
      - 1945 Jul 12, Phil Harris for Kyser, fragment, typescript, 2 p. (Box 9)
      - 1945 Jul 18, 28 p. fragment, typescript, 2 p. (Box 9)
      - 1945 Jul 18, fragment, typescript copy, 7 p. (Box 9)
      - 1945 Jul 25, anno., rev., 26 p. (Box 9)
      - 1945 Aug 1, anno., rev., 28 p. (Box 9)
      - 1945 Aug 2, Phil Harris for Kyser, fragment, typescript, 2 p. (Box 9)
      - 1945 Aug 8, rev., 29 p. (Box 9)
      - 1945 Aug 15, rev., 24 p. (Box 9)
      - 1945 Aug 22, anno., 27 p. (Box 9)
      - 1945 Aug 23, Phil Harris for Kyser, fragment, typescript, 1 p. (Box 9)
      - 1945 Sep 12, rev., 29 p. (Box 9)
      - 1945 Sep 13, Phil Harris for Kyser, fragment, typescript, 1 p. (Box 9)
      - 1945 Sep 19, rev., 29 p. (Box 9)
      - 1945 Oct 3, rev., 27 p. (Box 9)
      - 1945 Oct 10, rev., 26 p. (Box 10)
      - 1945 Oct 24, rev., 32 p. (Box 10)
      - 1945 Oct 31, rev., 25 p. (Box 10)
      - 1945 Oct 31, rev., 26 p. (Box 10)
      - 1945 Nov 7, rev., 26 p. (Box 10)
      - 1945?, rev., 20 p. (Box 10)
      - 1945?, fragment, typescript copy, anno., 8 p. (Box 10)
      - 1945?, Undated fragments, typescript copy, 13 p. (Box 10)
    - Kay Kyser spots on Parade of Stars
      - 1945 Oct 7, anno., rev., 4 p. (Box 10)
      - Undated, 1945; draft A, typescript rev., 6 p.; draft B, typescript copy anno., 4 p. (Box 10)
    - Mail Call (Armed Forces Radio Service)
      - 1945 Dec 19, rev., 39 p. (Box 10)
    - Martin and Lewis Show
      - 1949 Nov 15, rev., 31 p. (Box 10)
      - 1949 Nov 21, anno., rev., 28 p. (Box 10)
      - 1949 Nov 28, anno., 26 p. (Box 10)
      - Undated fragments, 1949; typescript, typescript copy rev., 4 p. (Box 10)
    - The Pepsodent Program, starring Bob Hope
      - 1938 Dec 11, Preview, 31 p. (Box 10)
      - 1939 Jan 1, Preview, anno. (Box 10)
      - 1939 Jan 10, anno., rev., 25 p. (Box 10)
      - 1939 Jan 10, revised, 26 p. (Box 10)
      - 1939 Jan 15, Preview, anno., rev., 33 p. (Box 10)
      - 1939 Jan 15, revised 8 p. (Box 10)
      - 1939 Jan 29, Preview, anno., rev., 35 p. (Box 10)
      - 1939 Jan 31, revised 27 p. (Box 10)
      - 1939 Jan 31, revised 8 p. (Box 10)
      - 1939 Feb 7, revised anno., 24 p. (Box 10)
      - 1939 Feb 19, anno., 30 p. (Box 10)
      - 1939 Feb 26, Preview, anno., 26 p. (Box 10)
      - 1939 Mar 5, Preview, anno., 33 p. (Box 10)
      - 1939 Mar 7, revised 24 p. (Box 10)
      - 1939 Mar 12, Preview, 34 p. (Box 10)
      - 1939 Mar 14, revised, 26 p. (Box 11)
      - 1939 Mar 19, Preview, anno., 30 p. (Box 11)
      - 1939 Mar 21, revised anno., 25 p. (Box 11)
      - 1939 Mar 26, Preview, anno., rev., 29 p. (Box 11)
      - 1939 Mar 26, 30 p. (Box 11)
      - 1939 Apr 2, Preview, anno., 34 p. (Box 11)
      - 1939 Apr 4, revised, 29 p. (Box 11)
      - 1939 Apr 9, Preview, anno., rev., 36 p. (Box 11)
      - 1939 Apr 11, revised 24 p. (Box 11)
      - 1939 Apr 16, Preview, anno., rev., 31 p. (Box 11)
      - 1939 Apr 18, revised 26 p. (Box 11)
      - 1939 Apr 25, revised 26 p. (Box 11)
      - 1939 Apr 30, 26 p. (Box 11)
      - 1939 May 2, Preview, anno., 29 p. (Box 11)
      - 1939 May 7, Preview, anno., 29 p. (Box 11)
      - 1939 May 16, revised, anno., 30 p. (Box 11)
      - 1939 May 23, revised, anno., 29 p. (Box 11)
      - 1939 May 28, Preview, anno., rev., 32 p. (Box 11)
      - 1939 May 30, revised, anno., 29 p. (Box 11)
      - 1939 Jun 4, Preview, anno., rev., 35 p. (Box 11)
      - 1939 Jun 6, revised, 23 p. (Box 11)
      - 1939 Jun 18, Preview, 33 p. (Box 11)
      - 1939 Sep 24, anno., rev., 36 p. (Box 11)
      - 1939 Sep 26, revised, anno., 23 p. (Box 11)
      - 1939 Oct 1, Preview, anno., 31 p. (Box 11)
      - 1939 Oct 8, anno., 34 p. (Box 12)
      - 1939 Oct 10, revised, 10 p. (Box 12)
      - 1939 Oct 15, anno., rev., 30 p. (Box 12)
      - 1939 Oct 17, revised 23 p. (Box 12)
      - 1939 Oct 22, Preview, anno., 35 p. (Box 12)
      - 1939 Oct 24, revised 18 p. (Box 12)
      - 1939 Oct 29, Preview, anno., 34 p. (Box 12)
      - 1939 Nov 7, revised, anno., 30 p. (Box 12)
      - 1939 Nov 14, revised 28 p. (Box 12)
      - 1939 Nov 19, Preview 33 p. (Box 12)
      - 1939 Nov 21, revised 26 p. (Box 12)
      - 1939 Nov 28, revised, anno., 25 p. (Box 12)
      - 1939 Dec 5, revised, anno., 25 p. (Box 12)
      - 1939 Dec 12, revised, anno., 24 p. (Box 12)
      - 1939 Dec 17, Preview, anno., 46 p. (Box 12)
      - 1939 Dec 24, Preview, anno., 47 p. (Box 12)
      - 1940 Jan 2, revised, anno., 27 p. (Box 12)
      - 1940 Jan 15, Preview 41 p. (Box 12)
      - 1940 Jan 16, revised, anno., 22 p. (Box 12)
      - 1940 Jan 21, Preview, anno., 36 p. (Box 12)
      - 1940 Jan 23, revised 25 p. (Box 12)
      - 1940 Feb 4, Preview, anno., 43 p. (Box 12)
      - 1940 Feb 6, revised, anno., 24 p. (Box 12)
      - 1940 Feb 11, anno., 35 p. (Box 12)
      - 1940 Feb 13, revised, anno., 29 p. (Box 12)
      - 1940 Feb 18, Preview, anno., 36 p. (Box 12)
      - 1940 Feb 20, revised, 27 p. (Box 13)
      - 1940 Feb 25, Preview, anno., 40 p. (Box 13)
      - 1940 Feb 27, revised, 24 p. (Box 13)
      - 1940 Mar 3, Preview, anno., rev., 34 p. (Box 13)
      - 1940 Mar 5, revised, anno., 25 p. (Box 13)
      - 1940 Mar 10, anno., 37 p. (Box 13)
      - 1940 Mar 12, 25 p. (Box 13)
      - 1940 Mar 17, Preview, 36 p. (Box 13)
      - 1940 Mar 19, revised, 24 p. (Box 13)
      - 1940 Mar 24, Preview, anno., 40 p. (Box 13)
      - 1940 Mar 26, revised, rev., 24 p. (Box 13)
      - 1940 Mar 31, Preview, anno., 40 p. (Box 13)
      - 1940 Apr 2, revised, 27 p. (Box 13)
      - 1940 Apr 7, Preview, anno., 40 p. (Box 13)
      - 1940 Apr 9, revised, 23 p. (Box 13)
      - 1940 Apr 14, anno., 44 p. (Box 13)
      - 1940 Apr 16, revised, anno., 24 p. (Box 13)
      - 1940 Apr 21, anno., 40 p. (Box 13)
      - 1940 Apr 23, revised, 22 p. (Box 13)
      - 1940 Apr 30, revised, 24 p. (Box 13)
      - 1940 May 1, revised, 24 p. (Box 13)
      - 1940 May 12, Preview, anno., 53 p. (Box 13)
      - 1940 May 14, revised, 27 p. (Box 13)
      - 1940 May 21, revised, 29 p. (Box 13)
      - 1940 May 26, Preview, 13 p. (Box 13)
      - 1940 Jun 2, Preview, 45 p. (Box 14)
      - 1940 Jun 4, revised, 30 p. (Box 14)
      - 1940 Jun 11, revised, 25 p. (Box 14)
      - 1940 Jun 18, revised, 36 p. (Box 14)
      - 1940 Sep 22, Preview, anno., 45 p. (Box 14)
      - 1940 Sep 24, revised, 26 p. (Box 14)
      - 1940 Sep 29, Preview, anno., 38 p. (Box 14)
      - 1940 Oct 13, Preview, 45 p. (Box 14)
      - 1940 Oct 15, revised, 24 p. (Box 14)
      - 1940 Oct 20, Preview, anno., 44 p. (Box 14)
      - 1940 Oct 22, revised, 26 p. (Box 14)
      - 1940 Oct 29, revised, 28 p. (Box 14)
      - 1940 Oct 27, Preview, 26 p. (Box 14)
      - 1940 Nov 3, 54 p. (Box 14)
      - 1940 Nov 24, Preview, 45 p. (Box 14)
      - 1940 Nov 24, Preview, anno., 47 p. (Box 14)
      - 1940 Nov 26, revised, 27 p. (Box 14)
      - 1940 Dec 1, Preview, 48 p. (Box 14)
      - 1940 Dec 3, revised, anno., 24 p. (Box 14)
      - 1940 Dec 8, Preview, anno., 50 p. (Box 14)
      - 1940 Dec 22, Preview, anno., 53 p. (Box 14)
      - 1940 Dec 24, revised, 24 p. (Box 14)